<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Goce Anastasovski</title>
    <link>https://ganastasovski.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Goce Anastasovski</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ganastasovski.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Conferences</title>
      <link>https://ganastasovski.com/conferences/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Nov 2020 22:14:49 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ganastasovski.com/conferences/</guid>
      <description>Technical Talks Code Review A Software Engineer&amp;rsquo;s Best Friend - Link to Talk  DroidconAPAC, December 2020 GDG DevFest Italia, November 2020 DroidconEMEA, October 2020 DC Android Meetup, July 2020  Journal Articles  Katerina Goseva-Popstojanova and Goce Anastasovski &amp;ldquo;Characterization and classification of malicious Web traffic&amp;rdquo; In: Journal of Computer &amp;amp; Security  Conference Proceedings   Goce Anastasovski and Katerina Goseva-Popstojanova “Classification of Partially Labeled Malicious Web Traffic in the Presence of Concept Drift” In: The IEEE 8th International Conference on Software Security and Reliability-Companion (SERE-C), San Francisco, USA, June 30 - July 2, 2014 CA, USA: International Institute of Informatics and Systemics</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://ganastasovski.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Nov 2020 15:36:51 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ganastasovski.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Hey everyone, thank you for visiting my page. My name is Goce I am a Mobile Engineer at Alarm.com where I currently lead a team of iOS and Android engineers. After several years working on an app that lets you control IoT devices I took a break and spend some time working on Capital Ones’s banking app. In my free time, I am either working on side projects or conference talks.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>